you
think of humanity in the platter that's
one order
any biological organism is it's at worth
itself it will die the whole world
should know that there is no winner in
the war
no one will win we are all losers
godhardt eight
when children behave in ways that
disgraceful the way that we live our
lives today cannot lead for tomorrow
what people can do to this children it's
absolutely unbelievable you're living at
such a critical moment we don't have
another generation to wait if we
continue business as usual the Arctic
will be ice-free more and more people
realize that their path that the United
States is on right now is not
sustainable issues that kills there's
only time it will speak quickly
in the name of God
you know there's a lot to meet that but
I think everyone senses the extreme
urgency
[Music]
you have an ID at the moment United
Association where we have to make a
joint what does it mean to look in the
face of a world that seems to be going
rapidly in the wrong direction and say
no we're going to switch course I'm
going to make happen from time to time
these evolutionary leap occur and it
seems like this may be the moment
there's some shift going on throughout
the region and we're talking everywhere
from North Asia to Southeast Asia to
India you know where there's a sort of
movement taking place there are more
organizations forming themselves all
over this planet it's in every country
it's in every economic sector it's every
kind of person it's in every city and
there's no leader there's no
spokesperson there's no ideology the
biggest commitment in human history
Warren Buffett made a historic gift of
more than 30 billion dollars to the Bill
and Melinda Gates Foundation the top
goal being going after the health and
poverty issues are just pledged three
billion dollars to fight global warming
please welcome on our satellite Sir
Richard Branson Solano sources YouTube's
lead singer and a very well known a
leading philanthropist and their new
initiative is called product red and
they have gotten some major companies
like Apple the gap and they're all on
board to Friday's this year's Nobel
Peace Prize goes to Bangladeshi
economist Muhammad Yunus and the Grameen
Bank he founded back in 1983 they've
lifted millions of people out of poverty
particularly women through very small
loans micro credit financing is
estimated to have helped about seventeen
million people worldwide one person
making a very big difference in this
world
I feel we're going through a major
positional period I introduced
legislation to create a cabinet-level
Department of Peace we can make
compassion part of the understanding of
the work of a government one day we wake
up and discover we have family the
scientists coming around and saying yeah
we're seeing that and the flow of the
universe is unity and coherence and that
we're all connected
everything's waking up awakening our
connection to something larger than
ourselves
people have been there social change
over beyond around the world
hope is a beautiful way young people in
particular have a lot of hope Gandhi
said if we were to have true peace in
the world it must begin with the
children the more interconnected we are
the more we can build a global network
of young leaders you don't need to be
left there to be a leader
don't have to have a Nobel Peace Prize
in your hand to be a leader that
leadership is great about them the world
is going to change the only question is
how's it going to change is it going to
go
for better or for worse and that's
entirely up to us you know sometimes we
think of like oh well oh my god to be an
activist you've got your martyr and
you've got to suffer and it's going to
be so harder hell no man I hang out with
the coolest Cabrio people unconscious
before white spirits if it's a web 5 he
says you can dance he was like thank you
for watch and I want young people around
the world know that yeah making a change
making the world a better place it is
not only your responsibility it is your
joy it is your blessing it's your gift
it's your opportunity to make your life
mean something so take it we're going
round the bend into the comment
keep your mind on it shine your mind all
don't give up on it
cuz you know who you wanted to I'm
talking about I'm talking buddy you told
him bad news buddy you rotten bastard
knew you will come to keep your mind on
it sand on my doll don't give up on it
cuz you know hoe you wanted to I'm
talking bad boy combat your way don't
give up on it